<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artists on Dusk Records Aotearoa</title>
    <link>/artists/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Artists on Dusk Records Aotearoa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:53:08 +1200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/artists/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[vexxed] in my head</title>
      <link>/artists/vexxedinmyhead/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/vexxedinmyhead/</guid>
      <description>[vexxed] in my head are Carlos Antonio of ODD and Humaniser and John Mason of Stars and the Underground and Humaniser.
Based in tamaki makaurau, this project is quite unique and with the studio as a focal point material and ideas are passed between the pair with Carlos&amp;rsquo;s remixing ability to the fore dark electronic dancefloor bass driven grooves are created.
An EP release is planned, major motifs lyrically include alchemy representing change and the deconstruction of the self and emerging rejuvenated and new.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stars and the Underground</title>
      <link>/artists/starsandtheunderground/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/starsandtheunderground/</guid>
      <description>Stars and the Underground are a four piece band from Auckland, New Zealand.
They play a unique brand of Post Punk incorporating Shoegaze textures and Dark Electronic and Cold Wave vibes.
Our journey thus far has been about building a sound of which now we feel we are beginning to understand, as at 2022 after being dreadfully restricted by Covid19, we are now ready to share our new material which represents the band as it now exists the camaraderie and shared musical connection we have made during difficult times.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
