<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Stars and the Underground</title>
        <link>/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Stars and the Underground</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 11:53:06 +1200</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Transmissions: Blog Update 2</title>
            <link>/posts/update2/</link>
            <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 11:53:06 +1200</pubDate>
            
            <guid>/posts/update2/</guid>
            <description>I thought it would be a good idea to start posting and letting people interested in our music what was happening.
Naturally out of habit or poor planning i&amp;rsquo;ve spent alot of time over the hotter months when everybody sensible is out either playing live or enjoying their holidays or concerts inside recording and working toward getting in shape for playing live again.
To date the album &amp;ldquo;Guardians of the Night&amp;rdquo; is well and truely on track with three tracks completed and another three over with John Mcdermott</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[
    <img src="/update2.png"  alt="Hello Friend"  class="center"  />


<p>I thought it would be a good idea to start posting and letting people interested in our music what was happening.</p>
<p>Naturally out of habit or poor planning i&rsquo;ve spent alot of time over the hotter months when everybody sensible is out either playing live
or enjoying their holidays or concerts inside recording and working toward getting in shape for playing live again.</p>
<p>To date the album &ldquo;Guardians of the Night&rdquo; is well and truely on track with three tracks completed and another three over with John Mcdermott<br>
presently.</p>
<p>Once he finishes his drums parts he sends them back for final track laying I send them back to him once i&rsquo;m finished for mix
and mastering.</p>
<p>I think the thing that has surprised me about the new material is the ease with which it straddles across the main genres we normally inhabit and a new one
we haven&rsquo;t before.</p>
<p>In saying that there is no conscious effort on my part to emulate anybody as after all this time I like to think Stars has is own appeal
and i&rsquo;ve wanted to showcase a certain diversity of sound which will hopefully be of interest to the listener and, a certain groove which in the past
we almost had but not quite which bodes well for live performances.</p>
<p>As for live perfomances we are talking to a few bands, but expect it will be a little while yet (but not too long) as we have to finish the album first
but as I say I am preparing for this mode switch now.</p>
<p>From the two John&rsquo;s&hellip;..</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Transmissions: Blog Update 1</title>
            <link>/posts/first_release/</link>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
            
            <guid>/posts/first_release/</guid>
            <description>Well here we are, in February this year (2023) I indicated that there would be new material coming.
We were planning to release an Ep but these plans were shelved as Cat left the band then I decided not to continue on in the form that we were in to maintain the integrity of what I was trying to do.
Also due to alot of personal illness, family commitments I decided it would best to take a break from live work so I could focus on recording.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[
    <img src="/single.png"  alt="Hello Friend"  class="center"  />


<p>Well here we are, in February this year (2023) I indicated that there would be new material coming.</p>
<p>We were planning to release an Ep but these plans were shelved as Cat left the band then I decided not to continue on in the form that we were in to maintain the integrity
of what I was trying to do.</p>
<p>Also due to alot of personal illness, family commitments I decided it would best to take a break from live work so I could focus on recording.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m happy to say that this has really paid off, John Mcdermott a long time friend and drummer agreed to jump on board and help out with the project and
recording.</p>
<p>This has gone so well infact we have enough material for a new album.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Guardians of the Night&rdquo;</p>
<p>The above image is taken from the cover of the first single of the album &ldquo;Lonely Black Hearts Dismay&rdquo;, which also features a remix by Elenor Rayner (Robots In Love).</p>
<p>We are planning live performances to support the release in 2024.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
