<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Stars and the Underground</title>
        <link>/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Stars and the Underground</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 11:53:08 +1200</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Transmissions: Blog Update 1</title>
            <link>/posts/first_release/</link>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
            
            <guid>/posts/first_release/</guid>
            <description>Well here we are, in February this year (2023) I indicated that there would be new material coming. We were planning to release an Ep but these plans were shelved as Cat left the band then I decided not to continue on in the form that we were in to maintain the integrity of what I was trying to do.
Also due to alot of personal illness, family commitments I decided it would best best to take a break from live work so I could focus on recording.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[
    <img src="/single.png"  alt="Hello Friend"  class="center"  />


<p>Well here we are, in February this year (2023) I indicated that there would be new material coming. We were planning to release an Ep
but these plans were shelved as Cat left the band then I decided not to continue on in the form that we were in to maintain the integrity
of what I was trying to do.</p>
<p>Also due to alot of personal illness, family commitments I decided it would best best to take a break from live work so I could focus on recording.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m happy to say that this has really paid off, John Mcdermott a long time friend and drummer agreed to jump on board and help out with the project and
recording.</p>
<p>This has gone so well infact we have enough material for a new album.</p>
<p>&ldquo;Guardians of the Night&rdquo;</p>
<p>The above image is taken from the cover of the first single of the album &ldquo;Lonely Black Hearts Dismay&rdquo;, which also features a remix by Elenor Rayner (Robots In Love).</p>
<p>We are planning live performances to support the release in 2024.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
