<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stars and the Underground</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Stars and the Underground</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 11:53:08 +1200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lonely Black Hearts - Single</title>
      <link>/releases/lonely_black_hearts_dismay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/releases/lonely_black_hearts_dismay/</guid>
      <description>Nosferatu Upon Tyne (Single) by Stars and the Underground   After two years away from playing live Stars and the Underground are looking forward to bringing their unique hybrid post-punk/synthwave sound with shoegaze textures back to the stage in 2025.
Members John Mason originally of Auckland band Winterland and John McDermott a drummer who has played with the likes of the Headless Chickens have teamed up to an record album “Guardians of the Night”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 12:08:39 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Stars and the Underground
Stars and the Underground is the the musical project of Auckland, New Zealand based singer songwriter John Mason. (ex Winterland circa 1999)
Our name suggests a duality between musical textures. Usual motifs include ethereal and dark musical tones. If you walked into a music store people might file us alongside other artists and styles but how do you categorise yourself?
If you must then I would prefer it to read something like Post Punk, Darkwave and Dark Synthwave and Shoegaze.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shows</title>
      <link>/shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/shows/</guid>
      <description>   Date Line Up Venue City/Country     April 2025 w/Other Voices Whammy Bar Auckland, NZ   Aug 2022 w/After The Flesh Wine Cellar Auckland, NZ   Jan 2022 Gathering Shadows Valhalla Wellington, NZ   Jul 2021 w/Lichtbeuger Thirsty Dog Auckland, NZ   Dec 2020 Concierto Solidario Radio Subte Lima Sur - Live Stream Lima, Peru   Sep 2020 Dark Shadows Nirvara Lounge Hamilton, NZ   Nov 2019 Shadow Play Moon 1 Wellington, NZ   Aug 2019 Freaking The Dog Thirsty Dog Auckland, NZ   July 2019 w/ Swallow The Rat, Mothra Whammy Bar Auckland, NZ   Jun 2019 w/ Sounds Like Winter The Townie Sydney, Au   Jun 2019 w/ Robots In Love The Tote Melbourne, Au   Jun 2019 w/ Lichtbeuger Thirsty Dog Auckland, NZ   Jan 2019 w/ Drab Majesty Whammy Backroom Auckland, NZ   Dec 2018 w/ Permanence Thirsty Dog Auckland, NZ   Aug 2018 w/ Lichtbeuger Ding Dong Lounge Auckland, NZ   Feb 2017 w/ Ikon, Sounds Like Winter, Disjectamembra Whammy Bar Auckland, NZ    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video</title>
      <link>/video/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/video/</guid>
      <description>**Lonely Black Hearts Dismay **   (DuskAotearoa)
The single enjoy!!
Concierto Solidario - Radio Subte Lima Sur(Peru) Live Stream   (Mark Wallbank)
This video was shot for Radio Subte Lima Sur and was played on a big screen at the benefit concert so that the disadvantaged children of Villa María del Triunfo could enjoy some Christmas cheer.
Thank you to the late Daniel D (DANIEL SIEMPRE PRESENTE), Cristian Murillo and Milagros Rivera who supported us by playing Nosferatu Upon Tyne during our single release 2020 during covid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nosferatu Upon Tyne - Single</title>
      <link>/releases/nosferatu_upon_tyne/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/releases/nosferatu_upon_tyne/</guid>
      <description>Nosferatu Upon Tyne (Single) by Stars and the Underground   The vampire motif is an attempt to reconcile the very strong emotion that is fear.
Released August 12, 2020
Credits
Written &amp;amp; Performed By:
John Mason - Vocals/Guitars
Sean O’Kane Connolly - Keyboards/Vocals
Cat Veen - Keyboards/Vocals
Ario Kimber Manufui - Bass/Vocals
John McDermott - Drums
Recorded and Mixed By: John McDermott @ Arch Hill Studios, Auckland
Mastered By: Simon Polinski @ Hesius Dome, Melbourne</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolution Circle - EP</title>
      <link>/releases/evolution_circle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/releases/evolution_circle/</guid>
      <description>Evolution Circle EP - AU/NZ Tour by Stars and the Underground   1 Echolocation 03:36
2 Have a Heart 02:49
3 Twilight by Design 03:50
4 Quiet Remix (By Ashes the Condition) 04:14
Limited Edition AU/NZ Tour Sampler
Released June 1, 2019
Credits
John Mason (Vocals,Guitars,Programming)
Sean O&amp;rsquo;Kane Connolly (Keyboards/Vocals)
Mark Wallbank (Keyboards/Samples)
Mixed By Darryn Harkness
Produced by Stars and the Underground &amp;amp; Darryn Harkness
Words and Music John Mason</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
