<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dusk Aotearoa</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dusk Aotearoa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 11:53:08 +1200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SATU usher in a new era</title>
      <link>/posts/stars_rehersals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/stars_rehersals/</guid>
      <description>(Photo Cred: Mark Wallbank)
Stars and the Underground will once again meet in the rehersal room to start working on their set and an as yet undetermined song to be released as a single.
The band is in high spirits and have been wildly investing in new equipment with a view to refining the bands sound we look forward to seeing what emerges.
There will be some live shows announced once we are happy with where things are at and we hope to hook up with a few acts weve been talking to since last year about playing together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Single For VIMH</title>
      <link>/posts/first_release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/first_release/</guid>
      <description>(Photo Cred: Mark Wallbank)
Vexxed in my Head is proud to announce the first single off the new Ep &amp;ldquo;Boomer Tech&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Lonely Black Hearts Dismay&amp;rdquo; will be released soon. The track was mixed and mastered by Ant Bannister (Sounds Like Winter, Sequential Zero and Mantravision Productions) in Sydney.
The accompanying video was shot by Mark Wallbank of Paranormal New Zealand and Hieronymous Bosch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 12:08:39 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Dusk Aotearoa is a New Zealand (Aotearoa) based artist collective specialising in Post-Punk, Darkwave and Dark Electronic Music.
John Mason is pictured here with long time friend, collaborator, photographer and videographer Mark Wallbank he works with us on our projects.
Mark was the founder of Club Bizzare a Darkend Label Based in New Zealand home to Hieronymous Bosch and also founded Paranormal Research Group Haunted Auckland.
Rather than functioning as a old school record label that signs people, we more foster mutually beneficial relationships with other artists, encouraging them to work with us playing live and helping to build our respective audiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VEXXED in my head</title>
      <link>/artists/vexxedinmyhead/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/vexxedinmyhead/</guid>
      <description>VEXXED in my head is the solo project John Mason of Stars and the Underground and Winterland.
Based in tamaki makaurau, major motifs lyrically include alchemy representing change and the deconstruction of the self and emerging rejuvenated and new.
2023 will see the release of our new EP &amp;ldquo;Boomer Tech&amp;rdquo;
The music can be described as a Dark Synthwave with a good smattering of Bass IV.
 The tracklisting:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stars and the Underground</title>
      <link>/artists/starsandtheunderground/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/starsandtheunderground/</guid>
      <description>Stars and the Underground are a four piece band from Auckland, New Zealand.
They play a unique brand of Post Punk incorporating Shoegaze textures and Dark Electronic and Cold Wave vibes.
Our journey thus far has been about building a sound of which now we feel we are beginning to understand.
As of 2022 after being dreadfully restricted by Covid19, we are now ready to share our new material which represents the band as it now exists the camaraderie and shared musical connection we have made during difficult times.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
