<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dusk Aotearoa</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dusk Aotearoa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:53:08 +1200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 12:08:39 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Dusk Aotearoa is a New Zealand (Aotearoa) based artist collective specialising in Post-Punk, Darkwave and Dark Electronic Music.
John Mason is pictured here with long time friend, collaborator, photographer and videographer Mark Wallbank he works with us on our projects.
Mark was the founder of Club Bizzare a Darkend Label Based in New Zealand home to Hieronymous Bosch and also founded Paranormal Research Group Haunted Auckland.
Rather than functioning as a old school record label that signs people, we more foster mutually beneficial relationships with other artists, encouraging them to work with us playing live and helping to build our respective audiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VEXXED in my head</title>
      <link>/artists/vexxedinmyhead/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/vexxedinmyhead/</guid>
      <description>VEXXED in my head is the solo project John Mason of Stars and the Underground.
Based in tamaki makaurau, major motifs lyrically include alchemy representing change and the deconstruction of the self and emerging rejuvenated and new.
Steeped in sybolism the work has its heart rooted in experimentation.
The music is designed for the ethereal dark dancefloor!!
John has also been working with Carlos (ODD, Humaniser) who has been remixing the tracks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2022 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stars and the Underground</title>
      <link>/artists/starsandtheunderground/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/starsandtheunderground/</guid>
      <description>Stars and the Underground are a four piece band from Auckland, New Zealand.
They play a unique brand of Post Punk incorporating Shoegaze textures and Dark Electronic and Cold Wave vibes.
Our journey thus far has been about building a sound of which now we feel we are beginning to understand, as at 2022 after being dreadfully restricted by Covid19, we are now ready to share our new material which represents the band as it now exists the camaraderie and shared musical connection we have made during difficult times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winterland</title>
      <link>/artists/winterland/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 11:53:08 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artists/winterland/</guid>
      <description>Winterland (now defunct).
Labels &amp;amp; Distribution Flying Out (NZ), Heartland Records(Australia), Cyberdelia Records(Greece), Darkcell Digital(UK and Europe)
Winterland originally consisted of Mike Caulfield, Glynn Beaumont and Barry Morton, laterly joined by John Mason and Ross Harris who came togther to form the original band. A rehersal room on Quay Street and almost monthly shows marked our first years in existence.
Gradually as we built our name an audience which culminmated in our first EP release Ceremony, and with its release a distribution deal with Flying Out and a top ten hit Dreamtime on 95bfm thanks to the kind support of Renee Jones and Phil Armstrong.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
